

Morten Amundsen

SECURITY ANALYST . MSc STUDEN

Moholtlia 2A, 7033 Trondheim, Norway

□ (+47) 458 83 216 | 🗷 m.amundsen@pm.me | 🏕 mortenamundsen.me | 🖸 mortea15 | 🛅 mortenkamundsen

Summary.

Currently pursuing my final semester of an MSc in Information Security at NTNU, Gjøvik, while working part-time as an Information Security Analyst at Sportradar. I have experience with Security Operations, development, scripting/automation, and computer security. I'm curious, and I love to learn and solve challenges.

For my Master's thesis, I'm developing a system to automate the process of handling user incident reports based on Machine Learning and Natural Language Processing.

Education

NTNU (Norwegian University of Science and Technology)

Gjøvik, Norway

MSc in Information Security

Aug. 2018 - Jun. 2020

- Track of study: Information Security Management
- · See my LinkedIn profile for all courses.

UiA (University of Agder)

Kristiansand, Norway

Jan. - May. 2018, Jan. - Jun. 2017

Aug. 2015 - Jun. 2018

B.S. IN IT AND INFORMATION SYSTEMS

See my Linked In profile for all courses

• See my LinkedIn profile for all courses.

Skills

Security Application Security, Reverse Engineering, Threat Hunting, Log Analysis, Risk Management

DevOps AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Swarm, Git **Back-end** Express, Django, Flask, REST API

Operative Systems Linux, Windows

Programming Python, Node.js, JAVA, C#

Scripting Python, JavaScript, Bash, PowerShell

Languages Norwegian, English

Experience _____

Sportradar ASTrondheim, NorwayInformation Security AnalystJun. 2018 - Present

• Part-time employment working remotely. Full-time during vacations.

- · Development of security automation tools
- Threat Hunting / OSINT
- · Incident handling
- Risk Assessments
- Security Policies

ASSISTANT TEACHER

• Application Security Assessments

Decentralize IT Kristiansand, Norway

LEAD DEVELOPER Sep. 2017 - Jun. 2018

- Internship as a full-stack developer.
- Developed a cross-platform smartphone application based on the Steem blockchain, as well as a RESTful API backend.
- Working with the technologies Xamarin. Forms, React. js, Node. js, MongoDB, AWS and nginx.

University of Agder Kristiansand, Norway

• Assistant Teacher in the course IS-213; Open Source Software.

• Assistant Teacher in the course IS-110; Object Oriented Programming 2.

April 16, 2020 Morten Amundsen · Curriculum Vitae

Elektroimportøren AS Trondheim, Norway

Warehouse worker

- Part-time employment during vacations.
- Warehouse worker, seller and cashier.
- Working with logistics, order handling, Visma, sales and cashier.

ICA Supermarked Nardo Trondheim, Norway

CASHIER

Part-time employment as a cashier.

Televita AS Trondheim, Norway

TELEMARKETER

Part-time employment as a telemarketer.

Jan. 2014 - Apr. 2014

Apr. 2014 - Aug. 2015

Jun. 2016 - Jan. 2020

Certifications

The University of Nebraska at Omaha

Omaha, Nebraska, U.S.

CERTIFICATE IN IT ADMINISTRATION Jan. 2017